sircon.com 2017-07-06

# Privacy Policy | Sircon Solutions | Vertafore

You are using an out-of-date browser which is unsupported. For the best viewing experience, please upgrade to the latest version of one of the following browsers:  
[ Google Chrome](https://www.google.com/chrome/browser/desktop/) [ Mozilla Firefox](http://www.getfirefox.com/) [ Internet Explorer](http://www.microsoft.com/windows/internet-explorer/default.aspx) Hide

Updated: May 2, 2011

This policy covers Sircon.com (the "Site"). Other Vertafore web properties may have site specific privacy policies.

### Notice Regarding Collection and Use of your Personal Information

Personally identifiable information collected on this Site will be used to operate the Site and to provide the service(s) or carry out the action(s) you have requested or authorized. Additionally, Vertafore, Inc. and its controlled subsidiaries and affiliates ("Vertafore"), may use personal information to provide you with information about other Vertafore products and services.

The Site may collect certain information about your visit, such as the name of the Internet service provider and the Internet Protocol (IP) address through which you access the Internet; the browser you are using; the date and time you access the Site; the pages that you access while at the Site and the Internet address of the web site from which you linked directly to our site. This information is used to help improve the Site, analyze trends, and administer the Site.

Our web pages may provide links to unaffiliated third-party web sites. Since we do not control these web sites, we encourage you to review the policies of these third-party sites.

### Security of your Personal Information

Vertafore is committed to protecting the security of your personal information. To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. If social security numbers are collected by one of our sites, we protect the confidentiality, prohibit unlawful disclosure, and by limit access to the social security numbers.

### Transfer of your Personal Information

Except as otherwise described in this statement, personal information you provide via the Site will not be sold or shared outside of Vertafore.

Vertafore may disclose personal information if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Vertafore or the Site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Vertafore and our family of Web Services and Sites; or (c) act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of Vertafore employees or agents, users of Vertafore products or services, or members of the public.

### Use of Cookies

The Site uses 'cookies' so that we can recognize you and determine when you revisit Vertafore, and to provide a more personalized experience. A "cookie" is a small amount of data, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier, that our Site stores on the hard drive of your computer through your browser. Most browsers are set up to accept cookies, but you can usually change your browser settings to refuse them. Vertafore does not use cookies to retrieve personal information about you from your computer.

The Site uses 'cookies' so that we can recognize you and determine when you revisit Vertafore, and to provide a more personalized experience. A "cookie" is a small amount of data, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier, that our Site stores on the hard drive of your computer through your browser. Most browsers are set up to accept cookies, but you can usually change your browser settings to refuse them. Vertafore does not use cookies to retrieve personal information about you from your computer.

Vertafore uses cookies to:

  * Recognize you so that you can log in to our Site and access your account information.
  * Evaluate how many people return to our Site and measure the traffic to various areas of the Site.
  * Track the way you use our promotions, contests, and sales.
  * Personalize a user's experience on the Site and target our advertisements based on your current or previous use of our web site and any keywords you use on internet search engines to locate our Site.
  * Identify to third-party advertisers that you have visited the Site, so that these third-party advertisers may serve ads on our behalf.

### Choice of Future Communications

From time to time, Vertafore, Inc. and its controlled subsidiaries and affiliates may send you information about product and service offerings that may be of interest to you. At such a time, you will be given an opportunity to opt-out of future communications.

## Protection of Children's Personal Information

Vertafore.com is intended for a general audience and we do not knowingly collect personal information from those under the age of 13.

### Changes to this Statement

We may occasionally update this privacy statement. When we do, we will also revise the "Updated" date at the top of the privacy statement. We encourage you to periodically review this privacy statement to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. Your continued use of the Site constitutes your agreement to this privacy statement and any updates.

### Contact and Enforcement Information

Vertafore welcomes your comments regarding this privacy statement. If you have questions regarding this statement, please contact Vertafore at infosec@vertafore.com.

If you believe that Vertafore has not adhered to this privacy statement, please contact us at infosec@Vertafore.com or via postal mail at the address provided below, and we will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and remedy the problem.

Vertafore, Inc. (Attention Legal Department)  
11724 NE 195th Street  
Bothell, WA 98011
